idownloader.com 2011-11-23

# iDownloader | Fast Download Manager Accelerator - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us.

iDownloader Ltd. and its affiliates ("iDownloader", "we" or "us") are committed to protecting your privacy. We collect three types of user information: General Statistical Information, Automatically Collected Information, and Personal Identifying Information; we are providing you with this policy to inform you of how we use and, in limited circumstances, disclose such information.

Collection, Use and Disclosure of General Statistical Information and Automatically Collected Information

When you visit our website we gather certain general information, such as frequency of downloads, number of hits on our web site, and usage statistics with respect to our software products. This information is referred to throughout this policy as "General Statistical Information". We use and store this data only on a collective basis, in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This data helps us to determine how and the extent to which certain parts of our website and software are used. The stored General Statistical Information does not contain any Personal Identifying Information about you or any of our other users.

When you open an HTML email message from us or install a third party application offered by us during installation of the iDownloader software, we automatically record certain data usage technology, including cookies (defined below) and IP addresses. Such data include the email message you opened and the third party application you installed. This information is referred to throughout this policy as "Automatically Collected Information." We store this data on an individual basis but it is used only in summary form. This data helps us evaluate the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. ?The stored Automatically Collected Information does not contain any Personal Identifying Information about you or any of our users.

Collection and Use of Personal Identifying Information

In addition to collecting General Statistical Information, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, street address and email address. This is to enable us to respond to your requests and needs. Information that can reasonably be used to identify you is referred to in this policy as "Personal Identifying Information".

When you provide us Personal Identifying Information in an e-mail, fax or by telephone such as when you request technical and other types of support, we use the information to locate your records and provide you with answers to your questions.

Also, when you submit information to us in the context of a technical support inquiry, Personal Identifying Information may be attached to the information submitted.

Please note that you should be aware the transmission of error reports or other attachments may include confidential information which should be removed prior to the transmittal as we do not accept responsibility for the inadvertent subsequent disclosure of such confidential information. When you ask to be placed on one of our mailing lists, we will use your e-mail address to send you messages relevant to that list.

We use third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary networking, storage, and related technology.

Disclosure of Personal Identifying Information

We may disclose your Personal Identifying Information to our subsidiaries and affiliated companies or with appropriate third parties to process transactions you initiate, including shipping products to you and invoicing for purchases made and to contact you on our behalf regarding your account or software you have licensed from us. Examples of such third parties are our order processing and fulfillment service providers, companies that provide us with support services, credit card processing companies, and third parties whose product or service you purchase, register for, use or acquire through us. We may also disclose your Personal Identifying Information to third parties if we are required to do so by law, or if we believe that such action is necessary to:

* Comply with legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order;
* Protect our rights and property; or 
* Protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our web site and/or iDownloader Ltd. software products.

We never loan, rent or sell your Personal Identifying Information to others.

Cookies

We may set and access cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies in a limited way to track usage on our site. We gather information about site use by our visitors through cookie technology on an anonymous basis and analyze it at an aggregate level only. We may share aggregate data with our advertising partners or other online services partners. Use of this data enables us to continually improve our website and our products to meet the needs of our users.

In addition, we may use temporary session cookies to track your progress through our order processing system, keeping track of information such as the contents of your shopping cart and address. These session cookies only exist for the duration of your browser session. Our advertising partners or other online services partners may use their own cookies.

Most web browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can modify your browser setting to accept or decline cookies. Some of our web pages may require that you accept cookies. If you choose not to accept cookies you will not be able to access those web pages.

For information on how to disable cookies you should consult the instructions that accompanied your web browser.

Third Party Web Sites

All iDownloader Ltd. websites (including but not limited to: www.iDownloader.com) may contain links to third-party web sites over which we have no control or responsibility regarding content, privacy policies, or practices. We suggest that you review the privacy policy applicable to any third party site that you visit. This privacy policy applies only to our own websites. Note that all on-line and telephone credit card orders for iDownloader Ltd. software products may be processed by a third party.

WebSite Security

Our websites utilizes industry standard security technology to protect the security, integrity, and privacy of Personal Identifying Information from unauthorized third-party access. The Personal Identifying Information resides behind a firewall with access restricted to authorized iDownloader Ltd. employees and their agents.

Changes to the iDownloader Ltd. Privacy Policy

iDownloader Ltd. may amend this policy at any time by posting the amended terms on our web site. All amended terms will be automatically effective without further notice, 10 days after they are first posted.
